Guide to the Papers of Lourdes Portillo, 1979¯2001 M1480
Stanford University. Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- Series 1: Paper Production Materials, 1979¯2001
  - La Ofrenda: The Days of the Dead
    - Budget: Professional Services, nd; 1.0 Items (Carton 81, Folder 41)
    - Budget: Travel Expenses, nd; 1.0 Items (Carton 81, Folder 42)
    - Budget: Travel Per Diem, nd; 1.0 Items (Carton 81, Folder 43)
    - Budget: Travel, nd; 1.0 Items (Carton 81, Folder 44)
    - Budget: Research/Books, nd; 1.0 Items (Carton 81, Folder 45)
    - Budget: Lourdes' other Income Honorarium, Etc., nd; 1.0 Items (Carton 81, Folder 46)
    - Budget: Legal & Accounting, nd; 1.0 Items (Carton 81, Folder 47)
    - Budget: Entertainment/Business/Calendar, 1.0 Items (Carton 81, Folder 48)
    - Research, nd; 1.0 Items (Carton 81, Folder 49)
    - Research: Chicano Information #1, nd; 1.0 Items (Carton 81, Folder 50)
    - Research: Chicano Rearch #2, nd; 1.0 Items (Carton 81, Folder 51)
    - Research: Festival Artes De Mexico ¯ Los Angeles, 1991; 1.0 Items (Carton 81, Folder 52)
    - Research: L. J. Skaggs & Mary C. Skaggs Foundation Annual Report (Research), 1.0 Items (Carton 81, Folder 53)
    - Research: Prof. Enrique Bustamante, nd; 1.0 Items (Carton 81, Folder 54)
    - Research: Historical Overview, nd; 1.0 Items (Carton 81, Folder 55)
    - Research: Origins of "Dias de los Muertos" ¯ Study Guide, nd; 1.0 Items (Carton 81, Folder 56)
    - Research: Study Guide Draft, nd; 1.0 Items (Carton 81, Folder 57)
    - Research: Draft Study Guides, nd; 1.0 Items (Carton 81, Folder 58)
    - Research: Voices of Mexico #2, 1986¯1987; 1.0 Items (Carton 81, Folder 59)
    - Research: Museo Nacional de Antropologia ¯ Permit for Research ¯ Magazine, 10/1987; 1.0 Items (Carton 81, Folder 60)
    - Research: Lourdes Notes for La Ofrenda, 1.0 Items (Carton 81, Folder 61)
    - Research: Misc. Articles, nd; 1.0 Items (Carton 81, Folder 62)
    - Research: La Danza Cosmica, nd; 1.0 Items (Carton 81, Folder 63)
    - Research: Cineaste Magazine, 1989; 1.0 Items (Carton 81, Folder 64)
    - Research: Pictures, nd; 1.0 Items (Carton 81, Folder 65)
    - Production: Fenton, Original Treatment, nd; 1.0 Items (Carton 82, Folder 1)
    - Production: Film Treatment, nd; 1.0 Items (Carton 82, Folder 2)
    - Production: Film Treatment, nd; 1.0 Items (Carton 82, Folder 3)
    - Production: Revised Treatment, nd; 1.0 Items (Carton 82, Folder 4)
    - Production: Film Treatment (Re¯Formatted Version), nd; 1.0 Items (Carton 82, Folder 5)
    - Production: Stock Footage ¯ Possibilities, nd; 1.0 Items (Carton 82, Folder 6)
    - Production: Resumes, nd; 1.0 Items (Carton 82, Folder 7)
    - Production: Key Personnel, nd; 1.0 Items (Carton 82, Folder 8)
    - Production: Crew List, nd; 1.0 Items (Carton 82, Folder 9)
    - Production: Amalia Mesa¯Bains, Ph.D. ¯ Advisor, nd; 1.0 Items (Carton 82, Folder 10)
    - Production: Dr. Famon Favela, Advisor, 1.0 Items (Carton 82, Folder 11)
    - Production: Faye Ginsburg, New York University, nd; 1.0 Items (Carton 82, Folder 12)
    - Production: Masters, Photos, nd; 1.0 Items (Carton 82, Folder 13)
    - Production: Graphics Originals, nd; 1.0 Items (Carton 82, Folder 14)
    - Production: Music Rights Release, nd; 1.0 Items (Carton 82, Folder 15)
    - Production: Sound Production Transfer Orders, Sound Work Reports, 1.0 Items (Carton 82, Folder 16)
    - Production: Cue Sheet Music, nd; 1.0 Items (Carton 82, Folder 17)
    - Production: Editor's Notes, nd; 1.0 Items (Carton 82, Folder 18)
    - Production: Editor's Notes Version 1 & 2, nd; 1.0 Items (Carton 82, Folder 19)
    - Production: Editor's Notes Version 1 & 2, nd; 1.0 Items (Carton 82, Folder 20)
    - Production: Shooting Notes, nd; 1.0 Items (Carton 82, Folder 21)
    - Production: Shooting Schedule, nd; 1.0 Items (Carton 82, Folder 22)
    - Production: Ideas ¯ "Dias de los Muertos", nd; 1.0 Items (Carton 82, Folder 23)
    - Production: Camera Reports ¯ Monaco Labs, nd; 1.0 Items (Carton 82, Folder 24)
    - Production: Permit to Film In Mexico, 1987; 1.0 Items (Carton 82, Folder 25)
    - Production: Travel Itinerary ¯ Lourdes Portillo, nd; 1.0 Items (Carton 82, Folder 26)
    - Production: Film Inventory ¯ Mexico City, nd; 1.0 Items (Carton 82, Folder 27)
    - Production: Mexico "Dia de los Muertos" Shoot, nd; 1.0 Items (Carton 82, Folder 28)
    - Production: Equipment List ¯ Sara Chin, nd; 1.0 Items (Carton 82, Folder 29)
    - Production: Graphics, nd; 1.0 Items (Carton 82, Folder 30)
    - Production: Stationary ¯ La Ofrenda, 1.0 Items (Carton 82, Folder 31)
    - Production: Stationary Sample, nd; 1.0 Items (Carton 82, Folder 32)
    - Production: Production Binder, 1.0 Items (Carton 82, Folder 33)
    - Scripts: Synopsis, nd; 1.0 Items (Carton 82, Folder 34)
    - Scripts: Transcripts ¯ English, nd; 1.0 Items (Carton 82, Folder 35)
    - Scripts: Transcripts ¯ Spanish (Some Translation), nd; 1.0 Items (Carton 82, Folder 36)
    - Scripts: Version en Espanol ¯ Narration & Int Transcripts, nd; 1.0 Items (Carton 82, Folder 37)
    - Scripts: Narration Version 2, Bilingual, nd; 1.0 Items (Carton 82, Folder 38)
    - Scripts: Bilingual Transcripts (Master), nd; 1.0 Items (Carton 82, Folder 39)
    - Scripts: Bilingual Transcripts (Copy), nd; 1.0 Items (Carton 82, Folder 40)
    - Scripts: Narration, nd; 1.0 Items (Carton 82, Folder 41)
    - Scripts: Narration Version 2 English, nd; 1.0 Items (Carton 82, Folder 42)
    - Scripts: Narration, Version 2 Spanish, nd; 1.0 Items (Carton 82, Folder 43)
    - Scripts: Spanish Subtitles, nd; 1.0 Items (Carton 82, Folder 44)
    - Scripts: Subtitles, Timing, nd; 1.0 Items (Carton 82, Folder 45)
    - Other: Cinematte, nd; 1.0 Items (Carton 82, Folder 46)
    - Professional Correspondence: Letters of Congratulation, 1991; 1.0 Items (Carton 82, Folder 47)
    - Professional Correspondence: Correspondence ¯ Spanish, 1.0 Items (Carton 82, Folder 48)
    - Professional Correspondence: Complimentary Letter ¯ Jim Gonzalez, Board of Supervisors, 1.0 Items (Carton 82, Folder 49)
    - Professional Correspondence: Correspondence ¯ From Lourdes Portillo, 1.0 Items (Carton 82, Folder 50)
    - Professional Correspondence: Correspondence, 1.0 Items (Carton 82, Folder 51)
    - Professional Correspondence: Old Correspondence, 1990; 1.0 Items (Carton 82, Folder 52)
    - Professional Correspondence: Professional Correspondence, 1989¯1990; 1.0 Items (Carton 82, Folder 53)
    - Professional Correspondence: Galerie de la Raza/Studio 24 ¯ S.F., 4/1987; 1.0 Items (Carton 82, Folder 54)
    - Professional Correspondence: Letters of Support, 1.0 Items (Carton 82, Folder 55)
    - Professional Correspondence: California State University, Sacramento, 2/1987; 1.0 Items (Carton 82, Folder 56)
    - Publicity: Press Packet (English), nd; 1.0 Items (Carton 82, Folder 57)
    - Publicity: Packet, nd; 1.0 Items (Carton 82, Folder 58)
    - Publicity: Press Packet Originals, nd; 1.0 Items (Carton 82, Folder 59)
    - Publicity: The Squealer Magazine ¯ Spring Summer 1991, Lourdes Portillo Interview, 1.0 Items (Carton 82, Folder 60)
    - Publicity: FAF ¯ Film Arts Foundation Media Catalogue, 1991; 1.0 Items (Carton 82, Folder 61)
    - Publicity: Press Reviews, nd; 1.0 Items (Carton 82, Folder 62)
    - Publicity: Interview with Lourdes Portillo, nd; 1.0 Items (Carton 82, Folder 63)
    - Publicity: Newspaper/Magazine Articles, nd; 1.0 Items (Carton 82, Folder 64)
    - Publicity: Cine Accion News ¯ S.F. ¯ Fall, 1989; 1.0 Items (Carton 82, Folder 65)
    - Publicity: Cine Accion News ¯ S.F. ¯ August¯November, 1990; 1.0 Items (Carton 82, Folder 66)
    - Publicity: Cine Works Directory ¯ A Latino Media Resource Guide, 1993; 1.0 Items (Carton 82, Folder 67)
    - Publicity: Crossroads Magazine #31, Oakland, 5/1993; 1.0 Items (Carton 82, Folder 68)
    - Publicity: La Ofrenda Brochures/Flyers, 1.0 Items (Carton 82, Folder 69)
    - Festivals/Exhibitions/Other: Selected Film Exhibitions, nd; 1.0 Items (Carton 83, Folder 1)
    - Festivals/Exhibitions/Other: Various Exhibitions, nd; 1.0 Items (Carton 83, Folder 2)
    - Festivals/Exhibitions/Other: Albuquerque Journal, 5/1991; 1.0 Items (Carton 83, Folder 3)
    - Festivals/Exhibitions/Other: American Museum of Natural History ¯ Margaret Mead Film Festival ¯ New York, 9/1990; 1.0 Items (Carton 83, Folder 4)
    - Festivals/Exhibitions/Other: Athens International Film & Video Festival, 1989; 1.0 Items (Carton 83, Folder 5)
    - Festivals/Exhibitions/Other: 11th Annual Atlanta Third World Film Festival, 10/1991; 1.0 Items (Carton 83, Folder 6)
    - Festivals/Exhibitions/Other: British Film Institute 33rd London Film Festival, 11/1989; 1.0 Items (Carton 83, Folder 7)
    - Festivals/Exhibitions/Other: 3rd Caribbean Film Festival, Martinique, 6/1992; 1.0 Items (Carton 83, Folder 8)
    - Festivals/Exhibitions/Other: CEPA Film Program ¯ San Francisco, nd; 1.0 Items (Carton 83, Folder 9)
    - Festivals/Exhibitions/Other: Center for the Arts Exhibition, 1995; 1.0 Items (Carton 83, Folder 10)
    - Festivals/Exhibitions/Other: Center for Regional Studies & the Southwest Hispanic Research Institute, nd; 1.0 Items (Carton 83, Folder 11)
    - Festivals/Exhibitions/Other: Chicano Moratorium Coalition Film Festival, August ¯ S.F.; August & September ¯ Berkeley, nd; 1.0 Items (Carton 83, Folder 12)
    - Festivals/Exhibitions/Other: 6th Annual Chicago Latino Film Festival, 1990; 1.0 Items (Carton 83, Folder 13)
    - Festivals/Exhibitions/Other: Cina Chicano ¯ Germany, 1998; 1.0 Items (Carton 83, Folder 14)
    - Festivals/Exhibitions/Other: Cina de Mestizaje ¯ The National Latino Film & Video Festival ¯ New York, 1991; 1.0 Items (Carton 83, Folder 15)
    - Festivals/Exhibitions/Other: 1st Festival ¯ Cine San Juan, Puerto Rico, 1988; 1.0 Items (Carton 83, Folder 16)
    - Festivals/Exhibitions/Other: Primer Festival ¯ Cine San Juan Book, San Juan, Puerto Rico, nd; 1.0 Items (Carton 83, Folder 17)
    - Festivals/Exhibitions/Other: Conference Of Latin Women Film & Video Makers, 1990; 1.0 Items (Carton 83, Folder 18)
    - Festivals/Exhibitions/Other: Denver Museum of Natural History Exhibit, 10/1990; 1.0 Items (Carton 83, Folder 19)
    - Festivals/Exhibitions/Other: Detroit Institute of Arts, Latin American Month, 10/1991; 1.0 Items (Carton 83, Folder 20)
    - Festivals/Exhibitions/Other: The Documentary Festival of New York, nd; 1.0 Items (Carton 83, Folder 21)
    - Festivals/Exhibitions/Other: Dryden Theatre ¯ Curtis Theatre, New York, 1991; 1.0 Items (Carton 83, Folder 22)
    - Festivals/Exhibitions/Other: El Museo del Barrio National Latin Film & Video Festival, New York, 1989; 1.0 Items (Carton 83, Folder 23)
    - Festivals/Exhibitions/Other: Este Lugar ¯ 1st Annual Border Film Festival ¯ New Mexico, nd; 1.0 Items (Carton 83, Folder 24)
    - Festivals/Exhibitions/Other: Exploratorium, San Francisco, nd; 1.0 Items (Carton 83, Folder 25)
    - Festivals/Exhibitions/Other: Festival 2000, San Francisco, 10/1990; 1.0 Items (Carton 83, Folder 26)
    - Festivals/Exhibitions/Other: Xi Festival Cinematografico Internacional del Uruguay, 4/1993; 1.0 Items (Carton 83, Folder 27)
    - Festivals/Exhibitions/Other: Festival de Films & Videos de Femmes ¯ Montreal, 4/1992; 1.0 Items (Carton 83, Folder 28)
    - Festivals/Exhibitions/Other: Festival International de Films de Femmes ¯ Creteil, France, 1990; 1.0 Items (Carton 83, Folder 29)
    - Festivals/Exhibitions/Other: Festival Latino in New York, 1987¯1989; 1.0 Items (Carton 83, Folder 30)
    - Festivals/Exhibitions/Other: Festival Magazine #7, 9/1993; 1.0 Items (Carton 83, Folder 31)
    - Festivals/Exhibitions/Other: 5th Annual Film Arts Festival, San Francisco, 11/1989; 1.0 Items (Carton 83, Folder 32)
    - Festivals/Exhibitions/Other: Filmanmeldung Entry Form (Berlin), nd; 1.0 Items (Carton 83, Folder 33)
    - Festivals/Exhibitions/Other: Films Charas Community Film Program, New York, 1993; 1.0 Items (Carton 83, Folder 34)
    - Festivals/Exhibitions/Other: Guadalupe Cultural Arts Center ¯ San Antoni0, Texas, Cine Festival, 1990; 1.0 Items (Carton 83, Folder 35)
    - Festivals/Exhibitions/Other: Hispanic Heritage Month Bilingual Activities & Program Guide, L.A., 9/1991; 1.0 Items (Carton 83, Folder 36)
    - Festivals/Exhibitions/Other: The Houston International Film Festival, 4/1989; 1.0 Items (Carton 83, Folder 37)
    - Festivals/Exhibitions/Other: Hot Springs Documentary Film Festival, 1996; 1.0 Items (Carton 83, Folder 38)
    - Festivals/Exhibitions/Other: International House of Philadelphia, Pa, nd; 1.0 Items (Carton 83, Folder 39)
    - Festivals/Exhibitions/Other: Latin American Film Festival, nd; 1.0 Items (Carton 83, Folder 40)
    - Festivals/Exhibitions/Other: The Metropolitan Museum of Art, New York, Mexico Splendors of Thirty Centuries, 10/1990; 1.0 Items (Carton 83, Folder 41)
    - Festivals/Exhibitions/Other: Museum of Modern Art Department of Film, New York, 3/1994; 1.0 Items (Carton 83, Folder 42)
    - Festivals/Exhibitions/Other: Oregon Art Institute ¯ Portland, Northwest Film & Video Center Screening, 10/1989; 1.0 Items (Carton 83, Folder 43)
    - Festivals/Exhibitions/Other: Sundance Institute 1989 United States Film Festival, 1.0 Items (Carton 83, Folder 44)
    - Festivals/Exhibitions/Other: UC Berkeley, University Art Museum, Pacific Film Archive, 11/1991; 1.0 Items (Carton 83, Folder 45)
    - Festivals/Exhibitions/Other: UC Berkeley Extension ¯ Screening, 10/1999; 1.0 Items (Carton 83, Folder 46)
    - Festivals/Exhibitions/Other: UCLA Film & Folklore Association Presents Vitas, 2/1991; 1.0 Items (Carton 83, Folder 47)
    - Festivals/Exhibitions/Other: UC Davis Chicana/Latina Research Project & Chicana Studies, 3/1993; 1.0 Items (Carton 83, Folder 48)
    - Festivals/Exhibitions/Other: UC Irvine Conference "Chicana Latina Filmmaking", 3/1992; 1.0 Items (Carton 83, Folder 49)
    - Festivals/Exhibitions/Other: University of California, Santa Cruz, Second Annual UCSC Women of Color Film Festival, 1.0 Items (Carton 83, Folder 50)
    - Festivals/Exhibitions/Other: UCLA Wight Art Gallery, L.A. ¯ Chicano Art, 11/1990; 1.0 Items (Carton 83, Folder 51)
    - Festivals/Exhibitions/Other: University of Michigan, Program in Film & Video Studies, nd; 1.0 Items (Carton 83, Folder 52)
    - Festivals/Exhibitions/Other: University of Minnesota ¯ Twin Cities ¯ Macarthur Interdisciplinary Program on Peace & International Cooperation, 1996; 1.0 Items (Carton 83, Folder 53)
    - Festivals/Exhibitions/Other: Unitarian Universalist Congegation, 10/1989; 1.0 Items (Carton 83, Folder 54)
    - Festivals/Exhibitions/Other: Visiting Artist Program ¯ University of Colorado at Boulder, nd; 1.0 Items (Carton 83, Folder 55)
    - Festivals/Exhibitions/Other: Whitney Museum of American Art 61, New American Film & Video Series, New York, 1/1992; 1.0 Items (Carton 83, Folder 56)
    - Festivals/Exhibitions/Other: The Ninth Annual Women's International Film & Video Festival, Chicago, 3/1990; 1.0 Items (Carton 83, Folder 57)
    - Festivals/Exhibitions/Other: Lourdes Portillo Appearances, 1992; 1.0 Items (Carton 83, Folder 58)
    - Festivals/Exhibitions/Other: USC School of Cinema ¯ Television ¯ Border Crossings, nd; 1.0 Items (Carton 83, Folder 59)
    - Festivals/Exhibitions/Other: L.A.C.E. ¯ Los Angeles Contemporary Exhibitions, nd; 1.0 Items (Carton 83, Folder 60)
    - Festivals/Exhibitions/Other: "Mexico: Splendors of 30 Centuries" ¯ Metropolitan Museum Of Art, Nyc, Ny, 1990¯1991; 1.0 Items (Carton 83, Folder 61)
    - Seminars: Los Angeles International Film Festival ¯ 1990 (Proposal), 1.0 Items (Carton 83, Folder 62)
    - Seminars: Robert Flaherty Seminar Evaluation ¯ International Film Seminars ¯ New York, nd; 1.0 Items (Carton 83, Folder 63)
    - Seminars: San Francisco Art Institute Multi¯Cultural Symposium, 10/1989; 1.0 Items (Carton 83, Folder 64)
    - Seminars: PBS Rocky Mountain Retreat, 5/1990; 1.0 Items (Carton 83, Folder 65)
    - Seminars: "Show the Right Thing" Conference, New York, 9/1989; 1.0 Items (Carton 83, Folder 66)
    - Distribution: Corporation for Public Broadcasting (CPB) Agreement, nd; 1.0 Items (Carton 83, Folder 67)
    - Distribution: KCET, La Program License Agreement, 1998; 1.0 Items (Carton 83, Folder 68)
    - Distribution: Eastern Educational Television Network (EEN) Contract, nd; 1.0 Items (Carton 83, Folder 69)
    - Distribution: Direct Cinema Limited ¯ Draft Contract, 1989; 1.0 Items (Carton 83, Folder 70)
    - Distribution: Direct Cinema Limited ¯ Summary of All Income & Expenses, 1990; 1992¯1996; 1.0 Items (Carton 83, Folder 71)
    - Distribution: Tapestry International, New York, nd; 1.0 Items (Carton 83, Folder 72)
    - Distribution: Contracts, nd; 1.0 Items (Carton 83, Folder 73)
    - Distribution, nd; 1.0 Items (Carton 83, Folder 74)
    - Distribution: Contacts, nd; 1.0 Items (Carton 83, Folder 75)
    - Distribution: Rentals/Sales, 1996; 1.0 Items (Carton 83, Folder 76)
    - Distribution: Rentals/Sales, 1993¯1994; 1.0 Items (Carton 83, Folder 77)
    - Distribution: Rental/Sales, 1991; 1.0 Items (Carton 83, Folder 78)
    - Distribution: Rentals/Sales, 1990; 1.0 Items (Carton 83, Folder 79)
    - Distribution: Rentals/Sales, 1989; 1.0 Items (Carton 83, Folder 80)
    - Distribution: Correspondence ¯ Video Purchase, 1.0 Items (Carton 83, Folder 81)
    - Distribution: Broadcast Standards, Inc., L.A., 9/1991; 1.0 Items (Carton 83, Folder 82)
    - Distribution: Cornell University, New York Latin American Studies Program, nd; 1.0 Items (Carton 83, Folder 83)
    - Distribution: LA ¯ Red Distribution, nd; 1.0 Items (Carton 83, Folder 84)
    - Distribution: SPOR ¯ Denmark, 1989; 1.0 Items (Carton 83, Folder 85)
    - Distribution: Invoice ¯ Photo Rights ¯ Vegetarian Times, Connecticut, 7/1996; 1.0 Items (Carton 83, Folder 86)
    - Distribution: Andrea Rosen Gallery, New York, 2/1991; 1.0 Items (Carton 83, Folder 87)
    - Distribution: Mailing Lists, nd; 1.0 Items (Carton 83, Folder 88)
    - Awards: American Film and Video Festival ¯ Blue Ribbon Award, 1.0 Items (Carton 83, Folder 89)
    - Awards: National Academy of Television Arts & Sciences ¯ Emmy Awards Dinner, New York, 9/1989; 1.0 Items (Carton 83, Folder 90)
    - Awards: Athens Center for Film & Video Prize Check, nd; 1.0 Items (Carton 83, Folder 91)
    - Awards: Humanities Network ¯ Grant Award ¯ winter 1988, 1.0 Items (Carton 83, Folder 92)
    - Awards: Vitas Film Festival Award, nd; 1.0 Items (Carton 83, Folder 93)
    - Awards: Black Maria Film & Video Festival, West Orange, New Jersey ¯ 1989 ¯ Director's Choice Selection, 1.0 Items (Carton 83, Folder 94)
    - Article: Photography, Identity, and Death in the Films of Lourdes Portillo by Barbara Mcbane, 1.0 Items (Carton 83, Folder 95)
    - Paper Materials attached to original film cans, 1987¯1988; 1.0 Folders (Carton 94, Folder 17)
    - Photocopies of original film cans, 1987¯1988; 1.0 Folders (Carton 94, Folder 18)
    - Paper Materials attached to original film cans, 1987¯1988; 1.0 Folders (Carton 95, Folder 17)
    - Photocopies of original film cans, 1987¯1988; 1.0 Folders (Carton 95, Folder 18)
    - Paper Materials attached to original film cans, 1987¯1988; 1.0 Folders (Carton 96, Folder 17)
    - Photocopies of original film cans, 1987¯1988; 1.0 Folders (Carton 96, Folder 18)
    - Paper Materials attachedto original film cans, nd; 16.0 Items (Carton 100, Folder 17)
    - Photocopies of original film cans, nd; 16.0 Items (Carton 100, Folder 18)
    - Lab Paperwork and note, 1.0 (Carton 112, Folder 8)
    - La Ofrenda ¯ paste up of flyer side 1, 1.0 (Carton 113, Folder 1)
    - La Ofrenda ¯ paste up of flyer side 2, 1.0 (Carton 113, Folder 2)
  - Columbus on Trial
    - Proposals: Introduction, nd; 1.0 Folders (Carton 40, Folder 1)
    - Proposals: Rockefeller Foundation, 1/1992; 1.0 Folders (Carton 40, Folder 2)
    - Proposals: FAF grant request, 12/1992; 1.0 Folders (Carton 40, Folder 3)
    - Proposals: POV submission form, 9/1993; 1.0 Folders (Carton 40, Folder 4)
    - Proposals: ACSN application, 7/1993; 1.0 Folders (Carton 40, Folder 5)
    - Budget: Donations: from Ms. Portillo, 1992; 1.0 Folders (Carton 40, Folder 6)
    - Budget: NEA's in¯kind contributions, 6/1992; 1.0 Folders (Carton 40, Folder 7)
    - Budget: Letters requesting support, 7/1991; 1.0 Folders (Carton 40, Folder 8)
    - Budget: Film budget, 8/1992; 1.0 Folders (Carton 40, Folder 9)
    - Budget: Copying expenses, nd; 1.0 Folders (Carton 40, Folder 10)
    - Budget: Insurance, nd; 1.0 Folders (Carton 40, Folder 11)
    - Budget: Invoices ¯ Xochitl¯Perales, nd; 1.0 Folders (Carton 40, Folder 12)
    - Budget: Petty cash (Estella Maria Teresa Garcia de la Noceda), nd; 1.0 Folders (Carton 40, Folder 13)
    - Budget: Petty cash reports & receipts, nd; 1.0 Folders (Carton 40, Folder 14)
    - Budget: Laurie Coyle: production coordinator ¯ bills, 1992; 1.0 Folders (Carton 40, Folder 15)
    - Budget: Lithograph payment, 2/1992; 1.0 Folders (Carton 40, Folder 16)
    - Budget: Entertainment, 1992; 1.0 Folders (Carton 40, Folder 17)
    - Budget: Postage, delivery expenses, 1992; 1.0 Folders (Carton 40, Folder 18)
    - Budget: Business expenses, 1992¯1993; 1.0 Folders (Carton 40, Folder 19)
    - Budget: Film festival invoice, 11/1992; 1.0 Folders (Carton 40, Folder 20)
    - Budget: Equipment rentals ¯ #504, nd; 1.0 Folders (Carton 40, Folder 21)
    - Budget: Studio GGP ¯ #504a, nd; 1.0 Folders (Carton 40, Folder 22)
    - Budget: Supplies & materials, prod. ¯ #505, nd; 1.0 Folders (Carton 40, Folder 23)
    - Budget: Wardrobe & makeup ¯ #505a, nd; 1.0 Folders (Carton 40, Folder 24)
    - Budget: Sets & props receipts ¯ #505b, nd; 1.0 Folders (Carton 40, Folder 25)
    - Budget: Production stills ¯ #505c, nd; 1.0 Folders (Carton 40, Folder 26)
    - Budget: Crew invoices #506, nd; 1.0 Folders (Carton 40, Folder 27)
    - Budget: Cast invoices ¯ #506d, nd; 1.0 Folders (Carton 40, Folder 28)
    - Budget: Catering, food per diem ¯ #508a, nd; 1.0 Folders (Carton 40, Folder 29)
    - Budget: Hotel ¯ #508d, nd; 1.0 Folders (Carton 40, Folder 30)
    - Budget: Banking records ¯ "Taxi, Taxi" ("Taxi, Taxi" was the 1st name given to this project)., nd; 1.0 Folders (Carton 40, Folder 31)
    - Research: Book: WGBH ¯ Columbus and the Age of Discovery, 1.0 Folders (Carton 40, Folder 32)
    - Research: Cineaste: vol. 19, #4, nd; 1.0 Folders (Carton 40, Folder 33)
    - Research: Advisors to Columbus video, nd; 1.0 Folders (Carton 40, Folder 34)
    - Research: Nuestro, 12/1979; 1.0 Folders (Carton 40, Folder 35)
    - Research: News clips ¯ 10/92, 10/1992; 1.0 Folders (Carton 40, Folder 36)
    - Production: Ms. Portillo's calendar, 1993; 1.0 Folders (Carton 40, Folder 37)
    - Production: Production notes ¯ katy, nd; 1.0 Folders (Carton 40, Folder 38)
    - Production: Script supervisor's daily logs & script notes, 7/1992; 1.0 Folders (Carton 40, Folder 39)
    - Production: Drafts of video project border, "taxi, taxi", 1.0 Folders (Carton 40, Folder 40)
    - Production: Synopsis, nd; 1.0 Folders (Carton 40, Folder 41)
    - Production: Script, nd; 1.0 Folders (Carton 40, Folder 42)
    - Production: Scripts, 7/1992; 1.0 Folders (Carton 41, Folder 43)
    - Production: Script/storyboard, nd; 1.0 Folders (Carton 40, Folder 44)
    - Production: Music rights, 3/1995; 1.0 Folders (Carton 40, Folder 45)
    - Production: Music cue sheet, 11/1993; 1.0 Folders (Carton 40, Folder 46)
    - Production: Sound logs, 8/1992; 1.0 Folders (Carton 40, Folder 47)
    - Production: Casting schedule, 7/1992; 1.0 Folders (Carton 40, Folder 48)
    - Production: Alessandro: set design ¯ columbus courtroom, 7/1992; 1.0 Folders (Carton 40, Folder 49)
    - Production: Spanish subtitles, nd; 1.0 Folders (Carton 40, Folder 50)
    - Production: Transcripts, nd; 1.0 Folders (Carton 40, Folder 51)